{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(4x + 1)}/{3} + {(x + 8)}/{(x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "2(2x^2 + 6x + 13)/3(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 1)}/{3} * {(x + 2)}/{(x + 2)} + {(x + 8)}/{(x + 2)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(x + 2)(4x + 1)}/{3(x + 2)} + {3(x + 8)}/{3(x + 2)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({2(x + 5)}/{3} + {2(x + 1)}/{(x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "2(x^2 + 10x + 13)/3(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({2(x + 5)}/{3} * {(x + 2)}/{(x + 2)} + {2(x + 1)}/{(x + 2)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({2(x + 2)(x + 5)}/{3(x + 2)} + {6(x + 1)}/{3(x + 2)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{3} - {(x + 7)}/{(4x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "4(3x^2 + 5x - 4)/3(4x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{3} * {(4x + 1)}/{(4x + 1)} - {(x + 7)}/{(4x + 1)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(4x + 1)(3x + 5)}/{3(4x + 1)} - {3(x + 7)}/{3(4x + 1)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(4x + 3)}/{2(2x + 3)} + {(x + 1)}/{(x + 6)}\\)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 37x + 24)/2(2x + 3)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 3)}/{2(2x + 3)} * {(x + 6)}/{(x + 6)} + {(x + 1)}/{(x + 6)} * {2(2x + 3)}/{2(2x + 3)}\\)\n\\({(x + 6)(4x + 3)}/{2(2x + 3)(x + 6)} + {2(2x + 3)(x + 1)}/{2(2x + 3)(x + 6)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(2x + 1)} + {2(2x + 3)}/{(4x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 30x + 17)/(4x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 1)} * {(4x + 11)}/{(4x + 11)} + {2(2x + 3)}/{(4x + 11)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({(4x + 11)(2x + 1)}/{(4x + 11)} + {2(2x + 3)}/{(4x + 11)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 3)} - {(3x + 4)}/{3(x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 15x + 23)/3(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 3)} * {3(x + 3)}/{3(x + 3)} - {(3x + 4)}/{3(x + 3)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({3(x + 3)(x + 3)}/{3(x + 3)} - {(3x + 4)}/{3(x + 3)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({4(x + 2)}/{(2x + 7)} + {2(x + 4)}/{(x + 6)}\\)", "answer": "2(4x^2 + 31x + 52)/(2x + 7)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({4(x + 2)}/{(2x + 7)} * {(x + 6)}/{(x + 6)} + {2(x + 4)}/{(x + 6)} * {(2x + 7)}/{(2x + 7)}\\)\n\\({4(x + 6)(x + 2)}/{(2x + 7)(x + 6)} + {2(2x + 7)(x + 4)}/{(2x + 7)(x + 6)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 1)} + {(x + 8)}/{(4x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 16x + 19)/(4x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 1)} * {(4x + 11)}/{(4x + 11)} + {(x + 8)}/{(4x + 11)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({(4x + 11)(x + 1)}/{(4x + 11)} + {(x + 8)}/{(4x + 11)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(3x + 11)}/{(x + 4)} + {(x + 6)}/{(4x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(13x^2 + 63x + 57)/(x + 4)(4x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 11)}/{(x + 4)} * {(4x + 3)}/{(4x + 3)} + {(x + 6)}/{(4x + 3)} * {(x + 4)}/{(x + 4)}\\)\n\\({(4x + 3)(3x + 11)}/{(x + 4)(4x + 3)} + {(x + 4)(x + 6)}/{(x + 4)(4x + 3)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({3(x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)} - {2(x + 2)}/{(2x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "(11x + 13)/(3x + 2)(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({3(x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(2x + 7)}/{(2x + 7)} - {2(x + 2)}/{(2x + 7)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)}\\)\n\\({3(2x + 7)(x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 7)} - {2(3x + 2)(x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 7)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({4(x + 2)} - {2(x + 3)}/{(2x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "2(4x^2 + 29x + 41)/(2x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({4(x + 2)} * {(2x + 11)}/{(2x + 11)} - {2(x + 3)}/{(2x + 11)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({4(2x + 11)(x + 2)}/{(2x + 11)} - {2(x + 3)}/{(2x + 11)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{(x + 5)} - {(3x + 7)}/{(2x + 9)}\\)", "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 2)/(x + 5)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{(x + 5)} * {(2x + 9)}/{(2x + 9)} - {(3x + 7)}/{(2x + 9)} * {(x + 5)}/{(x + 5)}\\)\n\\({(2x + 9)(2x + 3)}/{(x + 5)(2x + 9)} - {(x + 5)(3x + 7)}/{(x + 5)(2x + 9)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(4x + 7)}/{3} - {(x + 4)}/{4(x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(16x^2 + 57x + 44)/12(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 7)}/{3} * {4(x + 2)}/{4(x + 2)} - {(x + 4)}/{4(x + 2)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({4(x + 2)(4x + 7)}/{12(x + 2)} - {3(x + 4)}/{12(x + 2)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 1)}/{3} - {(x + 11)}/{(2x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "2(x^2 + 5x - 11)/3(2x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 1)}/{3} * {(2x + 11)}/{(2x + 11)} - {(x + 11)}/{(2x + 11)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(2x + 11)(x + 1)}/{3(2x + 11)} - {3(x + 11)}/{3(2x + 11)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(3x + 11)}/{3} + {2(x + 5)}/{(4x + 9)}\\)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 77x + 129)/3(4x + 9)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 11)}/{3} * {(4x + 9)}/{(4x + 9)} + {2(x + 5)}/{(4x + 9)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(4x + 9)(3x + 11)}/{3(4x + 9)} + {6(x + 5)}/{3(4x + 9)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(4x + 1)} + {(2x + 1)}/{3(x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 29x + 7)/3(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 1)} * {3(x + 2)}/{3(x + 2)} + {(2x + 1)}/{3(x + 2)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({3(x + 2)(4x + 1)}/{3(x + 2)} + {(2x + 1)}/{3(x + 2)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 1)}/{2} - {(2x + 7)}/{(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 6x - 7)/2(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 1)}/{2} * {(3x + 7)}/{(3x + 7)} - {(2x + 7)}/{(3x + 7)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({(3x + 7)(x + 1)}/{2(3x + 7)} - {2(2x + 7)}/{2(3x + 7)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 4)}/{2} + {(4x + 1)}/{2(x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(x + 1)(x + 9)/2(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 4)}/{2} * {2(x + 2)}/{2(x + 2)} + {(4x + 1)}/{2(x + 2)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({2(x + 2)(x + 4)}/{4(x + 2)} + {2(4x + 1)}/{4(x + 2)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 11)}/{3} - {(3x + 2)}/{(4x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 36x + 5)/3(4x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 11)}/{3} * {(4x + 1)}/{(4x + 1)} - {(3x + 2)}/{(4x + 1)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(4x + 1)(x + 11)}/{3(4x + 1)} - {3(3x + 2)}/{3(4x + 1)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 5)} - {3(x + 3)}/{(4x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "2(2x^2 + 12x + 13)/(4x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 5)} * {(4x + 7)}/{(4x + 7)} - {3(x + 3)}/{(4x + 7)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({(4x + 7)(x + 5)}/{(4x + 7)} - {3(x + 3)}/{(4x + 7)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({3(x + 3)}/{4} - {2(2x + 5)}/{3(x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 29x + 14)/12(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({3(x + 3)}/{4} * {3(x + 2)}/{3(x + 2)} - {2(2x + 5)}/{3(x + 2)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({9(x + 2)(x + 3)}/{12(x + 2)} - {8(2x + 5)}/{12(x + 2)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 5)} - {(4x + 7)}/{2(x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 12x + 23)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 5)} * {2(x + 3)}/{2(x + 3)} - {(4x + 7)}/{2(x + 3)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({2(x + 3)(x + 5)}/{2(x + 3)} - {(4x + 7)}/{2(x + 3)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(2x + 11)}/{(4x + 3)} + {(x + 4)}/{2(x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 45x + 34)/2(4x + 3)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 11)}/{(4x + 3)} * {2(x + 1)}/{2(x + 1)} + {(x + 4)}/{2(x + 1)} * {(4x + 3)}/{(4x + 3)}\\)\n\\({2(x + 1)(2x + 11)}/{2(4x + 3)(x + 1)} + {(4x + 3)(x + 4)}/{2(4x + 3)(x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 9)}/{2} + {3(x + 3)}/{(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 40x + 81)/2(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 9)}/{2} * {(3x + 7)}/{(3x + 7)} + {3(x + 3)}/{(3x + 7)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({(3x + 7)(x + 9)}/{2(3x + 7)} + {6(x + 3)}/{2(3x + 7)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(4x + 7)}/{(3x + 11)} - {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "(x + 5)/(3x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 7)}/{(3x + 11)} * {(3x + 11)}/{(3x + 11)} - {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 11)} * {(3x + 11)}/{(3x + 11)}\\)\n\\({(3x + 11)(4x + 7)}/{(3x + 11)(3x + 11)} - {(3x + 11)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 11)(3x + 11)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({2(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 10)} + {(x + 11)}/{(x + 6)}\\)", "answer": "(7x^2 + 77x + 170)/(3x + 10)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({2(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 10)} * {(x + 6)}/{(x + 6)} + {(x + 11)}/{(x + 6)} * {(3x + 10)}/{(3x + 10)}\\)\n\\({2(x + 6)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 10)(x + 6)} + {(3x + 10)(x + 11)}/{(3x + 10)(x + 6)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({3(x + 1)}/{2(x + 2)} + {(x + 6)}/{(x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "5(x + 3)/2(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({3(x + 1)}/{2(x + 2)} * {(x + 2)}/{(x + 2)} + {(x + 6)}/{(x + 2)} * {2(x + 2)}/{2(x + 2)}\\)\n\\({3(x + 2)(x + 1)}/{2(x + 2)(x + 2)} + {2(x + 2)(x + 6)}/{2(x + 2)(x + 2)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(4x + 9)}/{3} - {2(x + 5)}/{(x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 47x + 69)/3(x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 9)}/{3} * {(x + 11)}/{(x + 11)} - {2(x + 5)}/{(x + 11)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(x + 11)(4x + 9)}/{3(x + 11)} - {6(x + 5)}/{3(x + 11)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({3(x + 1)}/{2} + {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 48x + 35)/2(3x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({3(x + 1)}/{2} * {(3x + 11)}/{(3x + 11)} + {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 11)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({3(3x + 11)(x + 1)}/{2(3x + 11)} + {2(3x + 1)}/{2(3x + 11)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{3(x + 1)} + {(3x + 11)}/{(2x + 9)}\\)", "answer": "(15x^2 + 79x + 78)/3(x + 1)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{3(x + 1)} * {(2x + 9)}/{(2x + 9)} + {(3x + 11)}/{(2x + 9)} * {3(x + 1)}/{3(x + 1)}\\)\n\\({(2x + 9)(3x + 5)}/{3(x + 1)(2x + 9)} + {3(x + 1)(3x + 11)}/{3(x + 1)(2x + 9)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 6)}/{4} - {(x + 2)}/{2(x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(x^2 + 9x + 26)/4(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 6)}/{4} * {2(x + 5)}/{2(x + 5)} - {(x + 2)}/{2(x + 5)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({2(x + 5)(x + 6)}/{8(x + 5)} - {4(x + 2)}/{8(x + 5)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 5)}/{(3x + 7)} + {(4x + 9)}/{(3x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "(15x^2 + 81x + 118)/(3x + 7)(3x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 5)}/{(3x + 7)} * {(3x + 11)}/{(3x + 11)} + {(4x + 9)}/{(3x + 11)} * {(3x + 7)}/{(3x + 7)}\\)\n\\({(3x + 11)(x + 5)}/{(3x + 7)(3x + 11)} + {(3x + 7)(4x + 9)}/{(3x + 7)(3x + 11)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{(x + 11)} + {(x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(7x^2 + 26x + 27)/(x + 11)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{(x + 11)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)} + {(x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)} * {(x + 11)}/{(x + 11)}\\)\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 5)}/{(x + 11)(2x + 1)} + {(x + 11)(x + 2)}/{(x + 11)(2x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({3(x + 3)}/{2} - {(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 17x - 1)/2(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({3(x + 3)}/{2} * {(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)} - {(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 1)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({3(2x + 1)(x + 3)}/{2(2x + 1)} - {2(2x + 5)}/{2(2x + 1)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(4x + 9)}/{3} - {(2x + 9)}/{(3x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 65x + 72)/3(3x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 9)}/{3} * {(3x + 11)}/{(3x + 11)} - {(2x + 9)}/{(3x + 11)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(3x + 11)(4x + 9)}/{3(3x + 11)} - {3(2x + 9)}/{3(3x + 11)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 3)}/{(4x + 5)} + {(2x + 9)}/{(x + 10)}\\)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 59x + 75)/(4x + 5)(x + 10)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 3)}/{(4x + 5)} * {(x + 10)}/{(x + 10)} + {(2x + 9)}/{(x + 10)} * {(4x + 5)}/{(4x + 5)}\\)\n\\({(x + 10)(x + 3)}/{(4x + 5)(x + 10)} + {(4x + 5)(2x + 9)}/{(4x + 5)(x + 10)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 11)}/{(2x + 5)} + {(3x + 8)}/{(x + 9)}\\)", "answer": "(7x^2 + 51x + 139)/(2x + 5)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 11)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(x + 9)}/{(x + 9)} + {(3x + 8)}/{(x + 9)} * {(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)}\\)\n\\({(x + 9)(x + 11)}/{(2x + 5)(x + 9)} + {(2x + 5)(3x + 8)}/{(2x + 5)(x + 9)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 5)}/{4} + {(2x + 5)}/{(x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(x + 3)(x + 15)/4(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 5)}/{4} * {(x + 5)}/{(x + 5)} + {(2x + 5)}/{(x + 5)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({(x + 5)(x + 5)}/{4(x + 5)} + {4(2x + 5)}/{4(x + 5)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 1)} + {(2x + 7)}/{2(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 16x + 17)/2(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 1)} * {2(2x + 5)}/{2(2x + 5)} + {(2x + 7)}/{2(2x + 5)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({2(2x + 5)(x + 1)}/{2(2x + 5)} + {(2x + 7)}/{2(2x + 5)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({4(x + 1)}/{(3x + 8)} - {(x + 5)}/{(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(5x + 9)(x - 4)/(3x + 8)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({4(x + 1)}/{(3x + 8)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)} - {(x + 5)}/{(2x + 1)} * {(3x + 8)}/{(3x + 8)}\\)\n\\({4(2x + 1)(x + 1)}/{(3x + 8)(2x + 1)} - {(3x + 8)(x + 5)}/{(3x + 8)(2x + 1)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 10)} + {2(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 31x + 76)/(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 10)} * {(2x + 7)}/{(2x + 7)} + {2(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 7)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({(2x + 7)(x + 10)}/{(2x + 7)} + {2(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 7)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 3)}/{(3x + 2)} - {2(2x + 5)}/{(x + 8)}\\)", "answer": "-(11x^2 + 27x - 4)/(3x + 2)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 3)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(x + 8)}/{(x + 8)} - {2(2x + 5)}/{(x + 8)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)}\\)\n\\({(x + 8)(x + 3)}/{(3x + 2)(x + 8)} - {2(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 2)(x + 8)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 6)}/{2(2x + 3)} + {(2x + 7)}/{(x + 8)}\\)", "answer": "9(x^2 + 6x + 10)/2(2x + 3)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 6)}/{2(2x + 3)} * {(x + 8)}/{(x + 8)} + {(2x + 7)}/{(x + 8)} * {2(2x + 3)}/{2(2x + 3)}\\)\n\\({(x + 8)(x + 6)}/{2(2x + 3)(x + 8)} + {2(2x + 3)(2x + 7)}/{2(2x + 3)(x + 8)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{2} + {(x + 7)}/{(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 9x + 16)/2(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{2} * {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)} + {(x + 7)}/{(3x + 2)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({(3x + 2)(2x + 1)}/{2(3x + 2)} + {2(x + 7)}/{2(3x + 2)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 5)} + {(x + 8)}/{(3x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 17x + 13)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 5)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)} + {(x + 8)}/{(3x + 1)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({(3x + 1)(x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)} + {(x + 8)}/{(3x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{2(x + 5)} - {(2x + 11)}/{(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(2x^2 - 23x - 95)/2(x + 5)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{2(x + 5)} * {(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 3)} - {(2x + 11)}/{(2x + 3)} * {2(x + 5)}/{2(x + 5)}\\)\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 5)}/{2(x + 5)(2x + 3)} - {2(x + 5)(2x + 11)}/{2(x + 5)(2x + 3)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({2(x + 1)}/{3} + {(2x + 11)}/{(4x + 9)}\\)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 32x + 51)/3(4x + 9)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({2(x + 1)}/{3} * {(4x + 9)}/{(4x + 9)} + {(2x + 11)}/{(4x + 9)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({2(4x + 9)(x + 1)}/{3(4x + 9)} + {3(2x + 11)}/{3(4x + 9)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(3x + 10)}/{3(x + 1)} - {(x + 6)}/{2(x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 23x + 62)/6(x + 1)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 10)}/{3(x + 1)} * {2(x + 4)}/{2(x + 4)} - {(x + 6)}/{2(x + 4)} * {3(x + 1)}/{3(x + 1)}\\)\n\\({2(x + 4)(3x + 10)}/{6(x + 1)(x + 4)} - {3(x + 1)(x + 6)}/{6(x + 1)(x + 4)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{2} + {(3x + 8)}/{(x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 19x + 31)/2(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{2} * {(x + 5)}/{(x + 5)} + {(3x + 8)}/{(x + 5)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({(x + 5)(2x + 3)}/{2(x + 5)} + {2(3x + 8)}/{2(x + 5)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({2(2x + 5)}/{(x + 2)} + {3(x + 2)}/{(4x + 9)}\\)", "answer": "(19x^2 + 88x + 102)/(x + 2)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({2(2x + 5)}/{(x + 2)} * {(4x + 9)}/{(4x + 9)} + {3(x + 2)}/{(4x + 9)} * {(x + 2)}/{(x + 2)}\\)\n\\({2(4x + 9)(2x + 5)}/{(x + 2)(4x + 9)} + {3(x + 2)(x + 2)}/{(x + 2)(4x + 9)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(2x + 9)}/{4} - {(3x + 2)}/{2(x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 13x + 41)/4(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 9)}/{4} * {2(x + 5)}/{2(x + 5)} - {(3x + 2)}/{2(x + 5)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({2(x + 5)(2x + 9)}/{8(x + 5)} - {4(3x + 2)}/{8(x + 5)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 7)}/{2} - {(x + 10)}/{(4x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 31x + 15)/2(4x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 7)}/{2} * {(4x + 5)}/{(4x + 5)} - {(x + 10)}/{(4x + 5)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({(4x + 5)(x + 7)}/{2(4x + 5)} - {2(x + 10)}/{2(4x + 5)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({2(x + 2)} - {(3x + 10)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 17x + 6)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({2(x + 2)} * {(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 4)} - {(3x + 10)}/{(3x + 4)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({2(3x + 4)(x + 2)}/{(3x + 4)} - {(3x + 10)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(4x + 11)}/{4} - {(4x + 9)}/{(3x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 61x + 85)/4(3x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 11)}/{4} * {(3x + 11)}/{(3x + 11)} - {(4x + 9)}/{(3x + 11)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({(3x + 11)(4x + 11)}/{4(3x + 11)} - {4(4x + 9)}/{4(3x + 11)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 3)}/{(2x + 1)} + {(3x + 4)}/{(x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(7x^2 + 18x + 16)/(2x + 1)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 3)}/{(2x + 1)} * {(x + 4)}/{(x + 4)} + {(3x + 4)}/{(x + 4)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)}\\)\n\\({(x + 4)(x + 3)}/{(2x + 1)(x + 4)} + {(2x + 1)(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 1)(x + 4)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(3x + 2)}/{4} + {(x + 10)}/{(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 31x + 54)/4(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 2)}/{4} * {(3x + 7)}/{(3x + 7)} + {(x + 10)}/{(3x + 7)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({(3x + 7)(3x + 2)}/{4(3x + 7)} + {4(x + 10)}/{4(3x + 7)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 1)} + {(4x + 1)}/{2(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 10x + 3)/2(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 1)} * {2(2x + 1)}/{2(2x + 1)} + {(4x + 1)}/{2(2x + 1)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({2(2x + 1)(x + 1)}/{2(2x + 1)} + {(4x + 1)}/{2(2x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 10)}/{3} + {(4x + 9)}/{2(x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 34x + 47)/6(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 10)}/{3} * {2(x + 1)}/{2(x + 1)} + {(4x + 9)}/{2(x + 1)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({2(x + 1)(x + 10)}/{6(x + 1)} + {3(4x + 9)}/{6(x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(2x + 9)} - {(2x + 1)}/{(x + 6)}\\)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 19x + 53)/(x + 6)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 9)} * {(x + 6)}/{(x + 6)} - {(2x + 1)}/{(x + 6)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({(x + 6)(2x + 9)}/{(x + 6)} - {(2x + 1)}/{(x + 6)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{3} + {(2x + 1)}/{(x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 26x + 28)/3(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{3} * {(x + 5)}/{(x + 5)} + {(2x + 1)}/{(x + 5)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{3(x + 5)} + {3(2x + 1)}/{3(x + 5)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 11)}/{4} + {(x + 3)}/{(4x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 49x + 23)/4(4x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 11)}/{4} * {(4x + 1)}/{(4x + 1)} + {(x + 3)}/{(4x + 1)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({(4x + 1)(x + 11)}/{4(4x + 1)} + {4(x + 3)}/{4(4x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 2)}/{2} + {(3x + 2)}/{(x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(x + 1)(x + 10)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 2)}/{2} * {(x + 3)}/{(x + 3)} + {(3x + 2)}/{(x + 3)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({(x + 3)(x + 2)}/{2(x + 3)} + {2(3x + 2)}/{2(x + 3)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(4x + 5)} - {(4x + 3)}/{(x + 10)}\\)", "answer": "-(14x^2 + 11x + 5)/(4x + 5)(x + 10)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(4x + 5)} * {(x + 10)}/{(x + 10)} - {(4x + 3)}/{(x + 10)} * {(4x + 5)}/{(4x + 5)}\\)\n\\({(x + 10)(2x + 1)}/{(4x + 5)(x + 10)} - {(4x + 5)(4x + 3)}/{(4x + 5)(x + 10)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)} + {2(x + 3)}/{(x + 8)}\\)", "answer": "(x + 3)(5x + 18)/(2x + 5)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(x + 8)}/{(x + 8)} + {2(x + 3)}/{(x + 8)} * {(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)}\\)\n\\({(x + 8)(x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)(x + 8)} + {2(2x + 5)(x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)(x + 8)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(3x + 1)} - {(x + 5)}/{(x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 12x - 1)/(x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 1)} * {(x + 4)}/{(x + 4)} - {(x + 5)}/{(x + 4)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({(x + 4)(3x + 1)}/{(x + 4)} - {(x + 5)}/{(x + 4)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 5)}/{4} + {(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 25x + 39)/4(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 5)}/{4} * {(2x + 7)}/{(2x + 7)} + {(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 7)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({(2x + 7)(x + 5)}/{4(2x + 7)} + {4(2x + 1)}/{4(2x + 7)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({2(2x + 1)}/{(4x + 1)} - {(x + 8)}/{(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 - 17x - 2)/(4x + 1)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({2(2x + 1)}/{(4x + 1)} * {(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 3)} - {(x + 8)}/{(2x + 3)} * {(4x + 1)}/{(4x + 1)}\\)\n\\({2(2x + 3)(2x + 1)}/{(4x + 1)(2x + 3)} - {(4x + 1)(x + 8)}/{(4x + 1)(2x + 3)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 2)}/{(x + 7)} - {(x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(x^2 + x + 3)/(x + 7)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 2)}/{(x + 7)} * {(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)} - {(x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(x + 7)}/{(x + 7)}\\)\n\\({(2x + 5)(x + 2)}/{(x + 7)(2x + 5)} - {(x + 7)(x + 1)}/{(x + 7)(2x + 5)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 11)} + {(3x + 1)}/{(x + 9)}\\)", "answer": "(x^2 + 23x + 100)/(x + 9)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 11)} * {(x + 9)}/{(x + 9)} + {(3x + 1)}/{(x + 9)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({(x + 9)(x + 11)}/{(x + 9)} + {(3x + 1)}/{(x + 9)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(4x + 5)}/{2} + {(x + 2)}/{(x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 19x + 19)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 5)}/{2} * {(x + 3)}/{(x + 3)} + {(x + 2)}/{(x + 3)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({(x + 3)(4x + 5)}/{2(x + 3)} + {2(x + 2)}/{2(x + 3)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)} + {(4x + 1)}/{(x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(14x^2 + 16x + 5)/(3x + 1)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)} * {(x + 4)}/{(x + 4)} + {(4x + 1)}/{(x + 4)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)}\\)\n\\({(x + 4)(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(x + 4)} + {(3x + 1)(4x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(x + 4)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 1)}/{2(2x + 5)} - {2(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 8)}\\)", "answer": "-(13x^2 + 37x + 12)/2(2x + 5)(3x + 8)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 1)}/{2(2x + 5)} * {(3x + 8)}/{(3x + 8)} - {2(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 8)} * {2(2x + 5)}/{2(2x + 5)}\\)\n\\({(3x + 8)(x + 1)}/{2(2x + 5)(3x + 8)} - {4(2x + 5)(2x + 1)}/{2(2x + 5)(3x + 8)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(2x + 3)} - {(4x + 7)}/{2(x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 22x + 23)/2(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 3)} * {2(x + 5)}/{2(x + 5)} - {(4x + 7)}/{2(x + 5)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({2(x + 5)(2x + 3)}/{2(x + 5)} - {(4x + 7)}/{2(x + 5)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({2(x + 3)}/{3} - {(x + 10)}/{(x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 5x - 24)/3(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({2(x + 3)}/{3} * {(x + 1)}/{(x + 1)} - {(x + 10)}/{(x + 1)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({2(x + 1)(x + 3)}/{3(x + 1)} - {3(x + 10)}/{3(x + 1)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(3x + 11)}/{4} - {(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 9)}\\)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 37x + 95)/4(2x + 9)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 11)}/{4} * {(2x + 9)}/{(2x + 9)} - {(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 9)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({(2x + 9)(3x + 11)}/{4(2x + 9)} - {4(3x + 1)}/{4(2x + 9)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 5)}/{3(x + 2)} - {2(x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "-(3x^2 + 2x + 7)/3(x + 2)(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 5)}/{3(x + 2)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)} - {2(x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)} * {3(x + 2)}/{3(x + 2)}\\)\n\\({(3x + 1)(x + 5)}/{3(x + 2)(3x + 1)} - {6(x + 2)(x + 1)}/{3(x + 2)(3x + 1)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(3x + 7)}/{3} - {(4x + 5)}/{3(x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 12x + 16)/3(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 7)}/{3} * {3(x + 3)}/{3(x + 3)} - {(4x + 5)}/{3(x + 3)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({3(x + 3)(3x + 7)}/{9(x + 3)} - {3(4x + 5)}/{9(x + 3)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(4x + 1)}/{4} + {(2x + 3)}/{(x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 21x + 15)/4(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 1)}/{4} * {(x + 3)}/{(x + 3)} + {(2x + 3)}/{(x + 3)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({(x + 3)(4x + 1)}/{4(x + 3)} + {4(2x + 3)}/{4(x + 3)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)} - {1}/{2}\\)", "answer": "-1/2(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)} * {2}/{2} - {1}/{2} * {(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 3)}\\)\n\\({2(x + 1)}/{2(2x + 3)} - {(2x + 3)}/{2(2x + 3)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(4x + 7)}/{2} + {(3x + 10)}/{2(x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 30x + 45)/2(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 7)}/{2} * {2(x + 5)}/{2(x + 5)} + {(3x + 10)}/{2(x + 5)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({2(x + 5)(4x + 7)}/{4(x + 5)} + {2(3x + 10)}/{4(x + 5)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(2x + 11)}/{(x + 1)} + {(2x + 3)}/{3(x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 50x + 69)/3(x + 1)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 11)}/{(x + 1)} * {3(x + 2)}/{3(x + 2)} + {(2x + 3)}/{3(x + 2)} * {(x + 1)}/{(x + 1)}\\)\n\\({3(x + 2)(2x + 11)}/{3(x + 1)(x + 2)} + {(x + 1)(2x + 3)}/{3(x + 1)(x + 2)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 6)}/{3} + {3(x + 1)}/{(4x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)(2x + 17)/3(4x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 6)}/{3} * {(4x + 7)}/{(4x + 7)} + {3(x + 1)}/{(4x + 7)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(4x + 7)(x + 6)}/{3(4x + 7)} + {9(x + 1)}/{3(4x + 7)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(3x + 7)}/{(4x + 9)} - {(x + 2)}/{(4x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 14x - 11)/(4x + 9)(4x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 7)}/{(4x + 9)} * {(4x + 1)}/{(4x + 1)} - {(x + 2)}/{(4x + 1)} * {(4x + 9)}/{(4x + 9)}\\)\n\\({(4x + 1)(3x + 7)}/{(4x + 9)(4x + 1)} - {(4x + 9)(x + 2)}/{(4x + 9)(4x + 1)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({2(x + 2)} + {(2x + 3)}/{2(x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 14x + 11)/2(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({2(x + 2)} * {2(x + 1)}/{2(x + 1)} + {(2x + 3)}/{2(x + 1)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({4(x + 1)(x + 2)}/{2(x + 1)} + {(2x + 3)}/{2(x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({3(x + 2)}/{(x + 9)} - {(3x + 8)}/{(x + 11)}\\)", "answer": "2(2x - 3)/(x + 9)(x + 11)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({3(x + 2)}/{(x + 9)} * {(x + 11)}/{(x + 11)} - {(3x + 8)}/{(x + 11)} * {(x + 9)}/{(x + 9)}\\)\n\\({3(x + 11)(x + 2)}/{(x + 9)(x + 11)} - {(x + 9)(3x + 8)}/{(x + 9)(x + 11)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(2x + 5)}/{2} + {(x + 10)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "3(2x^2 + 9x + 15)/2(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 5)}/{2} * {(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)} + {(x + 10)}/{(3x + 5)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({(3x + 5)(2x + 5)}/{2(3x + 5)} + {2(x + 10)}/{2(3x + 5)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(3x + 1)}/{(x + 3)} - {(x + 3)}/{(x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "2(x^2 - x - 4)/(x + 3)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 1)}/{(x + 3)} * {(x + 1)}/{(x + 1)} - {(x + 3)}/{(x + 1)} * {(x + 3)}/{(x + 3)}\\)\n\\({(x + 1)(3x + 1)}/{(x + 3)(x + 1)} - {(x + 3)(x + 3)}/{(x + 3)(x + 1)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{2(2x + 5)} + {(3x + 4)}/{4(x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(10x^2 + 29x + 22)/4(2x + 5)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{2(2x + 5)} * {4(x + 1)}/{4(x + 1)} + {(3x + 4)}/{4(x + 1)} * {2(2x + 5)}/{2(2x + 5)}\\)\n\\({4(x + 1)(2x + 1)}/{8(2x + 5)(x + 1)} + {2(2x + 5)(3x + 4)}/{8(2x + 5)(x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 1)}/{2} + {3(x + 3)}/{(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 16x + 25)/2(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 1)}/{2} * {(3x + 7)}/{(3x + 7)} + {3(x + 3)}/{(3x + 7)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({(3x + 7)(x + 1)}/{2(3x + 7)} + {6(x + 3)}/{2(3x + 7)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(4x + 5)}/{(3x + 7)} + {(4x + 5)}/{2(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(4x + 5)(7x + 9)/2(3x + 7)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 5)}/{(3x + 7)} * {2(2x + 1)}/{2(2x + 1)} + {(4x + 5)}/{2(2x + 1)} * {(3x + 7)}/{(3x + 7)}\\)\n\\({2(2x + 1)(4x + 5)}/{2(3x + 7)(2x + 1)} + {(3x + 7)(4x + 5)}/{2(3x + 7)(2x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 11)}/{3} - {(2x + 9)}/{(4x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 43x + 28)/3(4x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 11)}/{3} * {(4x + 5)}/{(4x + 5)} - {(2x + 9)}/{(4x + 5)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(4x + 5)(x + 11)}/{3(4x + 5)} - {3(2x + 9)}/{3(4x + 5)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(3x + 8)} - {(4x + 3)}/{(4x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 43x + 37)/(4x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 8)} * {(4x + 5)}/{(4x + 5)} - {(4x + 3)}/{(4x + 5)} * {1}/{1}\\)\n\\({(4x + 5)(3x + 8)}/{(4x + 5)} - {(4x + 3)}/{(4x + 5)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)} - {(3x + 8)}/{(x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "-(5x^2 + 13x + 3)/(2x + 1)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)} * {(x + 5)}/{(x + 5)} - {(3x + 8)}/{(x + 5)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)}\\)\n\\({(x + 5)(x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)(x + 5)} - {(2x + 1)(3x + 8)}/{(2x + 1)(x + 5)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Subtract:\n\\({(3x + 10)}/{3} - {2(x + 3)}/{(3x + 10)}\\)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 54x + 82)/3(3x + 10)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(3x + 10)}/{3} * {(3x + 10)}/{(3x + 10)} - {2(x + 3)}/{(3x + 10)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(3x + 10)(3x + 10)}/{3(3x + 10)} - {6(x + 3)}/{3(3x + 10)}\\)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(4x + 7)}/{4} + {(2x + 7)}/{4(x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 17x + 21)/4(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 7)}/{4} * {4(x + 2)}/{4(x + 2)} + {(2x + 7)}/{4(x + 2)} * {4}/{4}\\)\n\\({4(x + 2)(4x + 7)}/{16(x + 2)} + {4(2x + 7)}/{16(x + 2)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 10)}/{3} + {(3x + 4)}/{(x + 6)}\\)", "answer": "(x^2 + 25x + 72)/3(x + 6)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 10)}/{3} * {(x + 6)}/{(x + 6)} + {(3x + 4)}/{(x + 6)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({(x + 6)(x + 10)}/{3(x + 6)} + {3(3x + 4)}/{3(x + 6)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 4)}/{2} + {(3x + 4)}/{(x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(x^2 + 11x + 12)/2(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 4)}/{2} * {(x + 1)}/{(x + 1)} + {(3x + 4)}/{(x + 1)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({(x + 1)(x + 4)}/{2(x + 1)} + {2(3x + 4)}/{2(x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(x + 3)}/{(x + 2)} + {2(x + 2)}/{(x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 14x + 17)/(x + 2)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(x + 3)}/{(x + 2)} * {(x + 3)}/{(x + 3)} + {2(x + 2)}/{(x + 3)} * {(x + 2)}/{(x + 2)}\\)\n\\({(x + 3)(x + 3)}/{(x + 2)(x + 3)} + {2(x + 2)(x + 2)}/{(x + 2)(x + 3)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({2(x + 3)}/{3} + {(3x + 5)}/{2(x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 29x + 39)/6(x + 2)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({2(x + 3)}/{3} * {2(x + 2)}/{2(x + 2)} + {(3x + 5)}/{2(x + 2)} * {3}/{3}\\)\n\\({4(x + 2)(x + 3)}/{6(x + 2)} + {3(3x + 5)}/{6(x + 2)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Add:\n\\({(4x + 11)}/{2} + {(x + 9)}/{3(x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 47x + 51)/6(x + 1)", "explanation": "Equalize the denominators\n\\({(4x + 11)}/{2} * {3(x + 1)}/{3(x + 1)} + {(x + 9)}/{3(x + 1)} * {2}/{2}\\)\n\\({3(x + 1)(4x + 11)}/{6(x + 1)} + {2(x + 9)}/{6(x + 1)}\\)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify"}
]}